<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/" xmlns:admin="http://webns.net/mvcb/" xmlns:rdf="http://www.w3.org/1999/02/22-rdf-syntax-ns#" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
	<channel>
		<title>Control4  Blog</title>
		<link>https://www.control4.com/</link>
		<description>Blog posts for Control4</description>
		<dc:language>en-gb</dc:language>
		<dc:creator>webteam@control4.com</dc:creator>
		<dc:rights>Copyright 2019</dc:rights>
		<admin:generatorAgent rdf:resource="http://www.pyrocms.com/"/>

								<item>
				<title>78 Home Automation Ideas</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/345/78-home-automation-ideas</link>
				<description><![CDATA[The possibilities for home automation are limitless, from lighting to home theater and more. Here are 78 home automation ideas to get you started!]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2019 03:01:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/345/78-home-automation-ideas</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME TRENDS</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Steps to a Successful Home Remodel</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/567/steps-to-a-successful-home-remodel</link>
				<description><![CDATA[As long as you plan, do your research, set a budget, and hire professionals, your renovation will be a seamless process that you may even find to be fun!]]></description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2019 16:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/567/steps-to-a-successful-home-remodel</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Connecting Technology and Design with a Smart Home OS</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/566/connecting-technology-and-design-with-a-smart-home-os</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Designers are needing to familiarize themselves with tech that, when added to their design repertoire, can bring new and amazing devices together to delight clients.
A foundational smart product that will revolutionize the way clients experience their home is one many designers might not have heard of: a smart home operating system.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 04 Oct 2019 16:43:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/566/connecting-technology-and-design-with-a-smart-home-os</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Living the High Life</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/565/living-the-high-life</link>
				<description><![CDATA[A penthouse on top of one of India’s tallest towers has been transformed into a smart home and personal nightclub-in-the-clouds for one of the country’s top financial high-flyers.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2019 21:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/565/living-the-high-life</guid>
				<category>HOME SMART HOME</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>A Beautiful Bend in the River</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/564/a-beautiful-bend-in-the-river</link>
				<description><![CDATA[The stunning “V House” on Australia’s Sunshine Coast brings a striking new angle to high-tech luxury design.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2019 21:09:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/564/a-beautiful-bend-in-the-river</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME STORIES</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Showroom Spotlight: A Lights Out Location in Indianapolis</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/563/showroom-spotlight-a-lights-out-location-in-indianapolis</link>
				<description><![CDATA[“Our current showroom in the Indiana Design Center is all about the demo. When we have a client in front of us, rather than starting with individual categories like audio/video or lighting, we incorporate it all into pre-programmed scenes that trigger independent technologies in the home to operate simultaneously. We start the experience at the front of the showroom by pressing the doorbell on the Control4 Door Station. When the doorbell rings, the music inside automatically pauses, then the touch screen lights up and immediately displays the camera from the door station as well as exterior lighting.”]]></description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2019 19:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/563/showroom-spotlight-a-lights-out-location-in-indianapolis</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME STORIES</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Showroom Spotlight: A Sunset (Boulevard) Showroom</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/562/showroom-spotlight-a-sunset-boulevard-showroom</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Malibu Wired has been behind some of the most outrageous smart home projects in the LA market, delivering dream systems day in and day out.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2019 18:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/562/showroom-spotlight-a-sunset-boulevard-showroom</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME TRENDS</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Joe Whitaker on the Intersection of Technology and Design</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/561/joe-whitaker-on-the-intersection-of-technology-and-design</link>
				<description><![CDATA[We sat down with Joe Whitaker to ask him about the design-build community and technology, what he sees as a successful project team, and his overall thoughts on smart home technology.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 20:48:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/561/joe-whitaker-on-the-intersection-of-technology-and-design</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>A Show&#45;Stopping Showroom: Georgia Home Theater</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/560/a-showstopping-showroom-georgia-home-theater</link>
				<description><![CDATA[New homeowners want to establish their own style in a new space, and long-standing residents want to inject some fun with a home renovation.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 19:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/560/a-showstopping-showroom-georgia-home-theater</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME TRENDS</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Toni Sabatino on Design + Technology</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/559/toni-sabatino-on-design--technology</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Interior designer and design thought leader Toni Sabatino believes that the key to design success lies in creating experience-focused spaces for her clients. We took a few minutes with her to find out more about how she sees the industry finding success with these collaborations.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2019 17:27:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/559/toni-sabatino-on-design--technology</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Emerald EVP Brian Pagel on Fostering Design and Technology Relationships</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/558/emerald-evp-brian-pagel-on-fostering-design-and-technology-relationships</link>
				<description><![CDATA[We sat down with Brian Pagel,  the Executive Vice President of Emerald Expositions, to learn more about his mission to facilitate necessary conversations and collaboration between design, construction, and technology.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 19:04:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/558/emerald-evp-brian-pagel-on-fostering-design-and-technology-relationships</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>SMART CARE FOR LOVED ONES</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/557/smart-care-for-loved-ones</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Intelligent devices are more than fancy gadgets; for the elderly, they also offer the promise of freedom. 

Advances in home automation products are making it easier to feel safer in our homes, automate routine tasks, and help us gain insight into our behavior. Security devices—like sensored door locks and streaming cameras—mean that the young at heart can stay in their own homes longer. Meanwhile, environmental sensors, like carbon monoxide detectors and automated stoves, can alert caretakers to potential hazards—even from afar.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 16:16:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/557/smart-care-for-loved-ones</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME TRENDS</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Architect Stace McGee on Sustainability and Smart Home Design</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/556/architect-stace-mcgee-on-sustainability-and-smart-home-design</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Throughout his career, architect Stace McGee has been working to transform homes and buildings into sustainable designs that are as environmentally friendly as they are beautiful. We sat down with this go-green enthusiast to learn more about his mission to bring construction and technology together into the future of sustainable design.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2019 01:28:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/556/architect-stace-mcgee-on-sustainability-and-smart-home-design</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>GETTING CONNECTED WITH CARLEY</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/555/getting-connected-with-carley</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Carley Knobloch has appeared on HGTV, CNN, the Today Show, and in Good Housekeeping, RedBook, and more. She and her husband share two children, Annie and Spencer, and a big, wooly pup named Marty. When she’s not covering food, fashion, travel, and technology, she’s making instrumental memories with the family (they are all musical virtuosos).]]></description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 20:11:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/555/getting-connected-with-carley</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME STORIES</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>LIVED&#45;IN LUXURY: CREATING A HOME THAT REFLECTS THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE IN IT</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/554/livedin-luxury-creating-a-home-that-reflects-the-people-who-live-in-it</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Nestled in sunny Napa Valley, a part of the country renowned for its lush wine vineyards, the sleek exterior of Adam and Tamera Housley’s home evokes a lavish, Tuscan manor. The interior, however, is sleek in a much more modern sense. A smart home system from Control4 is at the helm, allowing the pair complete control of everything, from the media they stream and room-level climate control to home security and lighting— and beyond.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 18:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/554/livedin-luxury-creating-a-home-that-reflects-the-people-who-live-in-it</guid>
				<category>SMART HOME STORIES</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>THE EVOLUTION OF HOME TECHNOLOGY</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/553/the-evolution-of-home-technology</link>
				<description><![CDATA[It was 1972 when my parents bought the first microwave on the block. Some neighbors gathered around to watch the first instant cooking machine on the market. They all loitered with bated breath as my father placed a single kernel of popcorn in the middle of the microwave and turned it on. They had time to have a few drinks and chat—the giant box took a long time to turn that single kernel into an edible bit of popcorn.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 19:54:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/553/the-evolution-of-home-technology</guid>
				<category>HOME SMART HOME</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>New features that Control4 customers will love in Smart Home OS 3</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/551/new-features-that-control4-customers-will-love-in-smart-home-os-3</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Control4 customers will love new personalization capabilities, new media features, and simplified navigation!]]></description>
								<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 21:40:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/551/new-features-that-control4-customers-will-love-in-smart-home-os-3</guid>
				<category>PERSONALIZED SMART HOME</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>HOME SECURITY GETS SMARTER, MORE SOPHISTICATED</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/505/home-security-gets-smarter-more-sophisticated</link>
				<description><![CDATA[When integrated as part of a home automation platform, a smart security system can provide extraordinary peace of mind and help your home run like a well-oiled machine. In addition to controlling more obvious security-related devices such as electronic door locks, surveillance cameras, and motion sensors, they can also keep your home safe from environmental dangers and infrastructure-related issues with sensors that report flooding, power shortages, and extreme swings in temperature.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 14:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/505/home-security-gets-smarter-more-sophisticated</guid>
				<category>PEACE OF MIND</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>MQA Music: Experience the original studio recording in your home</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/550/mqa-music-experience-100-of-the-original-studio-recording-in-your-home</link>
				<description><![CDATA[MP3 files deliver just 10% of the original studio recording. MQA reveals and authentically delivers every detail of the original recording.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/550/mqa-music-experience-100-of-the-original-studio-recording-in-your-home</guid>
				<category>AUDIO</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>​What is a Smart Home OS?</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/549/what-is-a-smart-home-os</link>
				<description><![CDATA[The benefits of technology in the home are virtually endless, but when these smart devices are managed by different apps and not unified by a powerful smart home OS, they can become tedious to manage. A smart home operating system, like Control4 Smart Home OS 3, is designed to unify hundreds of connected devices across the home and control them all from a single platform that gives homeowners the control and personalization you want while also offering concierge-style professional support when needed.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 22:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/549/what-is-a-smart-home-os</guid>
				<category>PERSONALIZED SMART HOME</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>SMART HOME MAGAZINE: SPECIAL EDITION ISSUE NOW AVAILABLE (FREE DOWNLOAD)</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/548/smart-home-magazine-special-edition-issue-now-available-free-download</link>
				<description><![CDATA[It’s really quite phenomenal to witness the many ways technology is converging into everyday design elements within the home and just how customized these products are becoming. Motorized cabinetry is allowing those with physical limitations to reach objects from above, kitchen countertop surfaces...]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 17:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/548/smart-home-magazine-special-edition-issue-now-available-free-download</guid>
				<category>HOME SMART HOME</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>What is C4Yourself Day?</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/547/what-is-c4yourself-day</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Getting hands-on with smart home products and really understanding them before your purchase is incredibly valuable. Understanding how products work and how they will fit into your home and into your life before you purchase makes an enormous difference when it comes to your long term satisfaction—and that is what #C4Yourself Day is all about!]]></description>
								<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 00:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/547/what-is-c4yourself-day</guid>
				<category>COMPANY</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Brandy Ketterer on Designing the Geist Reservoir Home</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/546/brandy-ketterer-on-designing-the-geist-reservoir-home</link>
				<description><![CDATA[Brandy Ketterer was the interior designer for the award-winning Geist Reservoir Home, and so we took a few minutes to chat with her about her experience as a designer, her roles in the Geist Reservoir project, and her thoughts on smart home design.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 17:23:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/546/brandy-ketterer-on-designing-the-geist-reservoir-home</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>A Theater Worthy of the Seven Kingdoms</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/545/a-theater-worthy-of-the-seven-kingdoms</link>
				<description><![CDATA[The ultimate immersive experience! Game of Thrones and fantasy fans will love this custom home theater completes with smart home capabilities.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 16:12:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/545/a-theater-worthy-of-the-seven-kingdoms</guid>
				<category>ENTERTAINMENT</category>
			</item>
					<item>
				<title>Expert Barry Dorsey on Designing Technology Clients will Love</title>
				<link>https://www.control4.com/blog/542/expert-barry-dorsey-on-designing-technology-clients-will-love</link>
				<description><![CDATA[We asked this Control4 Certified Showroom owner about his passion for technology, how he approaches the customer experience side of home automation, and what a designer or architect should do if they are looking to incorporate smart home technology into their projects.]]></description>
								<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 23:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid>https://www.control4.com/blog/542/expert-barry-dorsey-on-designing-technology-clients-will-love</guid>
				<category>BUILDING & DESIGN</category>
			</item>
					</channel>
</rss>
